{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Pool Tile Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/62553/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62553,"taskName":"Pool Tile - Install or Repair","taskDescription":"Install or Repair Pool Tile","xmTaskDescriptor":"Pool Tile Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"swimming pool swim inground tile","textMessagingName":"Pool Tile","rolloverLongDesc":"Installation or Repair of Swimming Pool Tile","rolloverShortDesc":"Install or Repair of Pool Tile","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Repair Swimming Pool Tile.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Pool Tile Repair \u0026 Replacement \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Pool Tile Installation","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":61,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Pool Tile Install or Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Pool Tile Install or Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Swimming Pool Tile Project","urlName":"Pool-Tile-Install-or-Repair","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pool Tile Repair \u0026 Replacement Services \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Pool Tile Installers","searchKeywords":"swimming,pool,swim,inground,hot,tub,sauna,tile","emcCategoryOid":-12070,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9190,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62553/":{"taskOID":62553,"originalTaskOID":62553,"setID":9190,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4864,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":3182,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503256,"questionDisplayText":"What type of tile do you need installed or repaired?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of tile do you need installed or repaired?","shortQuestionText":"What type of tile do you need installed or repaired?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4804,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Porcelain tile","answerDisplayText":"Porcelain tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204120,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Glass tile","answerDisplayText":"Glass tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3954,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Mosaic tile","answerDisplayText":"Mosaic tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204121,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick tile","answerDisplayText":"Brick tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6103,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stone tile","answerDisplayText":"Stone tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1991,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know -- would appreciate advice.","answerDisplayText":"Don't know -- would appreciate advice.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4864,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":3182,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3182,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5914,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Spa/hot tub","answerDisplayText":"Spa/hot tub","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":589,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":503256,"questionDisplayText":"What type of tile do you need installed or repaired?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of tile do you need installed or repaired?","shortQuestionText":"What type of tile do you need installed or repaired?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4804,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Porcelain tile","answerDisplayText":"Porcelain tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204120,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Glass tile","answerDisplayText":"Glass tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3954,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Mosaic tile","answerDisplayText":"Mosaic tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204121,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick tile","answerDisplayText":"Brick tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6103,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stone tile","answerDisplayText":"Stone tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1991,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know -- would appreciate advice.","answerDisplayText":"Don't know -- would appreciate advice.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4804,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Porcelain tile","answerDisplayText":"Porcelain tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204120,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Glass tile","answerDisplayText":"Glass tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3954,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Mosaic tile","answerDisplayText":"Mosaic tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":204121,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick tile","answerDisplayText":"Brick tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6103,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stone tile","answerDisplayText":"Stone tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1991,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know -- would appreciate advice.","answerDisplayText":"Don't know -- would appreciate advice.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}